In breaking news,
Chairman Huang of Ching He Temple,
who is currently being held in detention,
was found dead in his cell today.
Our preliminary investigation suggests
the cause of death was cardiac arrest.
An autopsy has ruled out homicide,
but this is yet to be officially…
Whether Chairman Huang's death
will affect the investigation…
NOTHING IS SO BEAUTIFUL AS SPRING
…has not been determined.
In other news, Mayor-elect…
"EARLY SPRING RAIN" BY HAN YU
…Tristan Hsueh is about to take office.
Today, he attended a charity event
in preparation for his inauguration.
Mayor-elect Hsueh announced that future
policies will prioritize the citizens…
-God damn it! Traitors!
-He will also strive…
No sense of honor.
One thing to your face,
another behind your back.
Don't be so angry.
Young people these days,
they're not like they used to be.
Forget about honor.
Just watch out they don't turn on you.
Fuck!
I treated him like a brother.
He treated me like dirt.
Fuck that!
We hope to be able to rebuild
and become a more caring society.
But this city's transformation's
not down to the mayor alone.
Only with the people's hard work
and wise counsel can this be achieved.
THE FIXERS
PRIMORDIAL FILES
-Congratulations on taking office.
-Thank you.
Everyone's efforts got us
to where we are today.
-You have our full support, sir.
-Congratulations, Mayor Hsueh.
-Miss Lu.
-Wow!
-The student surpassed the teacher.
-Thanks.
Your father has a successor.
My dad always says
I can learn a lot from you.
Mmm, don't say that.
So, the case is now in your hands.
-Let's find a good day to talk, all right?
-I look forward to it.
How are you? You settling into it?
I do start to wonder
if acting's just natural,
or due to training.
I know you don't like these events.
You heard anything further about the key?
It's dealt with.
-Now wait for the handover.
-Come on.
-Minister.
-Mayor, hello.
I'd like you to meet someone.
This is my brother Louis.
-Hello, Louis.
-Hello.
-I look forward to us working together.
-And so do I.
DOUBLE HAPPINESS
CHING HE TEMPLE OF TZU YUN CLIFF
MAYOR, TRISTAN HSUEH, MING YOUNG PARTY
I believe Ching He Temple
has always been a place
where citizens gather in faith and virtue.
Today, I came here to pray,
because I want Ching He's new start here
to align with our fortune.
Welcome back.
Have these two keys for your safekeeping,
Madam Chair.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You deserve a rest.
So, on behalf of the new government,
I hope that all future initiatives
align with the real concerns of everyone.
CELESTIAL
You must take back
the position that belongs to you.
Only you are qualified
to be Fixer Celestial.
Make both sides of the law be afraid.
And make sure they respect you.
After entering Kuang Ming Chamber,
find the compass of Primordial Files.
Align the dials in this specific order.
PRIMORDIUM
FROST'S DESCENT
East, Frost's Descent.
West, year 1909.
YEAR 1909
South, morning hours five to seven.
MORNING HOURS FIVE TO SEVEN
True North.
TRUE
With this passcode,
you can enter the secret tunnel
to the Primordial Files.
This date marks the day
Liao Tien-ting faked his death
and re-emerged
as the first Fixer Primordium.
Only
the Fixer Celestial and Fixer Primordium
have access to the secret tunnel.
Forced entry would trigger
the destruction of the Primordial Files.
But,
if the Primordial Files are controlled…
If she reclaims Ching He,
she'll have absolute control.
The balance of the scales
will be disturbed.
The files will give us
the necessary power.
We'd have influence
on both sides of the law… of the law…
Then neither Ching He nor Yeh Yueh Tong…
If I take over Ching He,
how do I deal with Madam Fan?
…could ever threaten the Hsueh clan.
And the genie won't go back in the bottle.
Let the next head of Ching He
worry about that.
What will occur when the Hsueh family
find out about the video?
They must find out who else knows.
And do you think they'll be spared?
SEVERAL DAYS AGO
If the right side of the law
gets their hands on the files,
their power will expand hugely.
They go to the wrong side of the law,
we'll see anarchy everywhere.
Only by holding each other in check
can you truly protect
the Hsueh family, your partner
and Ching He.
You're not wrong.
But the Primordial Files were never
in your possession, right?
My brother mentioned the secret tunnel
where the files are hidden.
Only Madam Fan knows how to open it.
No wonder you wanna catch her.
Do you have a plan?
Damn! We won't get
a chance like that again.
Fuck!
Sir Hong. You're a traitor as well.
I thank you on behalf of the chairman.
Lunar will definitely kill me.
I need you to help protect me.
So you and the chairman
colluded on a plan
to get the Primordial Files from Fan?
Gold stopped you killing Lunar.
He had good reason.
So you all had it planned out?
It might make more sense if he tells you.
Motherfucker!
You kept us in the dark all this time.
Madam Fan would have found out
if I hadn't done it.
I got a plan where we all get out safely.
I need you to join us.
Welcome back.
Have these two keys for your safekeeping,
Madam Chair.
Thank you for all your hard work.
You deserve a rest.
wind gusting]
Hands in the air.
Get out of the car.
Consider what you're doing.
Madam Fan's with Ching He.
I'll ask you one last time.
Where are the case files?
What do you want the files for?
She does things,
brutally and hastily.
I was right in my conjecture.
You've worked for her all this time.
How come you don't get it?
I can see what kind of person she is.
Of all those who have done
bad deeds for her,
are there any still here with us?
Before you kill me,
think carefully about
the person you're following.
Huh.
PRIMORDIUM
I can't believe it.
Being mayor is not enough for you?
You should have known beforehand.
Oh, I did.
But I didn't think you'd be so impatient.
And you're doing it yourself.
I learned the hard way.
The important things
you need to do yourself.
Then there's no messy loose ends.
You believe that, alone,
you can take charge of Ching He?
The other six leaders.
They'll be hard to deal with.
Who told you
I want to take charge of Ching He?
You were right.
One in the light, one in the dark.
Huh.
You chose Louis.
Killing a leader
in the Kuang Ming chamber of Ching He.
-You are aware of the consequences?
-Maybe.
I guess I'll find out.
A last wish.
Let me go in for a look.
Sorry. I'm not doing that.
I had no choice.
It had to be done.
He's here. Hello, Mayor.
Ah, hello there.
So good you're here.
I just brewed the tea.
Can I offer you a cup?
What's wrong?
Are you surprised the passageway
brought you back to this hall,
or are you surprised to see me?
Sir Hong asked me to give you this.
And, this stamp.
Once you ingest it,
it'll temporarily stop your heart.
Tea?
Aah!
So now San He's become Thackery's lackey?
You've been invited to drink tea.
so drink the fucking tea.
Kindness begets kindness,
and wrongs, wrongs.
Chairman.
Can I smoke?
Sure.
You'll be the first.
By summoning these people,
does that mean
you're not letting me leave?
Mayor, your decision will determine
whether you leave or stay.
Pin.
Please take these gentlemen
to the temple entrance.
I don't want anyone coming in.
Mayor.
Here's the thing.
Don't be fooled
by the tranquility in here.
Outside, a storm is raging.
Everyone's hard at work.
Yaah!
You can't hold a gun steady.
Why even try?
Hah!
Do you know what my symptoms are?
If I hold still…
…everything shakes.
Aah.
Fuck!
If I move while holding something,
it doesn't shake.
You fat fuck!
Fuck you! Aah!
Look on my works, ye mighty, and despair.
This one shot is the best of my career.
Chi!
Aah!
I fucking did it!
Aah.
So many tricks.
Was that even the real entrance?
We originally wanted to invite Madam Fan
to that passageway for a stroll.
CELESTIAL
PRIMORDIUM
Have you been partners all along?
Aah.
I dealt with Fan
so you could take control of Ching He.
But you colluded with Thackery
to betray me.
This is a video
from Hsu Ming-yi's dashcam.
You lied to me.
Hsu Ming-yi wasn't killed by Dad.
-This should be enough, right?
-Sir.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm not after money.
Then what is it?
I've been a legislative aide a long time,
hoping that one day,
I could be a legislator.
But I don't have the background.
I can't get elected.
But maybe…
if the Hsueh clan…
if they were to back me…
then I'd have a shot at it.
Are you threatening me now?
If the truth about
the Hsueh clan's involvement
in the Hsin Nan Redevelopment Zone
were to come out…
What do you think?
Would you be able to look at me
and do a deal?
Do you know what it takes to get this far?
To get where I am now?
That is exactly why collaborating with me
would suit us both.
Hmm?
Think carefully.
Hi, sweetie.
Nothin'.
Just talkin' with the councillor.
Okay. I'll be back soon.
Hey, don't worry.
Huh?
Yeah. I… I know.
Fuck!
I don't do deals.
I don't do deals. I don't do deals!
Hello? Hello? Honey?
Is something wrong?
ZOE
What was that sound? What's happened?
You were worried
something like this would turn up,
so you went to Yeh Yueh Tong to clean up
any evidence that could point to you.
And then to get rid of
anyone who knew anything.
All this time, you weren't trying
to cover up Dad's scandal.
You were trying to protect
your own political career.
Do you think I had to do nothing
to get where I am today?
People think
all that I achieved was down to Dad.
They don't see what I've done.
That Hsu Ming-yi guy
thought he had some dirt on me.
Could use me
as a stepping stone to climb up.
I'm not like you.
My margin for error is nil.
So Dad knows nothing about it?
You know something?
Sometimes I envy you.
You can do whatever you want.
But that you'd betray me…
My brother, out of everyone…
It's a shock.
This is the only way
that Ching He and the Hsueh clan
can achieve a balance
between the three parties.
How can you talk about balance
when you've joined forces with Ching He?
I just found this in the Primordial Files.
CASE FILE, DOUBLE SHADOW
TOP SECRET, THACKERY HUANG
I was originally just looking for
case files to use as a bargaining chip.
JIANGNAN, PRIMORDIUM, 1984
CELESTIAL ACCESS ONLY
But then I found
something related to you, Solar.
CASE FILE, DOUBLE SHADOW
TOP SECRET, THACKERY HUANG
You commissioned Primordium…
THACKERY HUANG
…to conveniently frame Madam Fan's dad
for the death of a Fixer.
We have discovered the Fixer's death
is connected all the way back to you.
And so we must postpone the handover
of the position of Fixer Celestial
to your daughter.
And that was just one of your many tricks.
No wonder you wanted
to get the files so badly.
You wanted to destroy the evidence.
If any of this information were to leak,
the authorities would
end up having a field day.
I didn't expect you'd make threats.
The third party you mentioned
is you, I'm guessing.
It's not a threat.
It's balance.
If any one party upsets the balance,
there is a corresponding reckoning.
You were always the smart one.
That's why I let you play around.
Not get too serious.
Because I knew once you did,
you would then be my greatest problem.
So from now,
Ching He can rely
on the Hsueh clan for support.
Do I have an option?
One moved the pieces.
The other swung the blade.
I'm just going with the flow.
I've also been checked by his pawn.
You really are better at everything.
I always said that one day,
I would help the Hsueh clan.
But I'd do it in the way I thought right.
Lines get blurry in this life
You're forced into the side
I, I see right through you
Howie.
Tell your mom it's all fine, huh?
Ah, you should have seen
how cool your dad was just now.
Aah!
I'll come get you later.
We are going home. Huh?
Hey. They let you go again?
What? You miss me?
I can't wait to get rid of you.
Get in.
I brought some buns.
You fucking with me again?
Aah.
This life's tough, but I'm tougher.
If the noodle business falls through,
I'd come back to all this.
Nobody gets out
without a few scars, anyway.
Mmm! We could get back
in the saddle if all else fails.
Oh.
Scallion one is still the best, isn't it?
ARCADE
Where to from here?
I wanna study abroad.
Get a fresh start.
Fan's death…
How will you handle that?
They'll only know Madam Fan's missing.
And you?
Will you stay with Ching He?
I'm the only one both sides won't touch.
If I stay, balance will be maintained.
Then won't you get stuck there?
Huh? Should I sell noodles
with you instead?
It's an option.
So the person finding it
hardest to leave is you.
I should go now.
See you around.
I've left Ben's stall to you.
Take care of it. Bye now.
Hey.
You goin' after her?
It's not a romantic drama, is it?
Shouldn't you go see a doctor?
Take me, then.
Let's go.
Aah.
So moody, this kid.
To maintain balance,
you need the black,
the white, and the gray.
Is this what you came up with
to protect your brother?
Delete all of Yeh Yueh Tong's
closed case files.
Ching He has leverage over my brother.
And I have leverage over them.
This is the only way
balance can be achieved.
Who's saying this?
Ching He's Fixer Gold?
Or the Hsueh clan's second son?
It's Louis.
I'm not sure if you can hear.
No doubt you'd say
that I betrayed Tristan.
All my life, I've tried
to prove that I'm his equal.
But after all this,
I've realized it wasn't worth it.
Spending all that time settling scores.
If you see Mom up there,
be nicer to her.
I have to say, your departure is
a great loss to Ching He.
Oh!
And you just got your marksmanship back.
Why would you want to turn your--
It's time to retire.
This illness is just going to get worse.
And my son's starting senior high.
Once they go to college, it's goodbye.
So he and I have got three good years.
That's true.
Honestly, though,
if it weren't for your help,
Ching He couldn't have
restored its stability.
You hear that?
Ah, Sir Hong.
How's your arm? Is it all right?
It is. I've had worse.
The money should definitely
be enough to comfortably retire.
-As long as you remember…
-Don't disclose anything about Ching He.
I know that. Don't you worry.
When I can, I'll come back to pray.
We'll drink tea together.
-You won't have to miss me.
-Quit while you're ahead.
-I'll walk you out.
-Right.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chairman.
Thank you, Sir Hong.
-Take care.
-You too. Bye now.
If you're feeling bored someday,
come back
and we'll take on a case together.
If you're ever bored, come to my place.
I'll cook you a nice meal.
Tomorrow sound okay?
All right, then.
All around, mountains and waters combine.
What's after that?
Shit.
Get yourself an education.
You're not so divine!
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
FELIX'S STIR-FRIED SWAMP EEL
Hey, Howie.
-Yeah?
-Come on.
YOU GET A SWEET DEAL
MY SWAMP EEL NOODLES
These noodles
and that tien-bu-la for the last table.
-Got it.
-Okay?
How do you like that?
Your swamp eel noodles are so popular
that you're still open.
Well, business is booming.
There's a line all day.
4.9 stars on Google.
How about that?
Oh yeah, I saw.
Don't reply online. Stop doing that.
Don't blame me, it's the customers.
They eat, then whine.
Yeah, sure.
Maybe I should bring my boyfriend.
He's a really good cook.
He might show you up.
Hey, what about, when Howie finishes
exams, we'll all come over there.
I'll cook for you
and your foreign boyfriend.
Where will you find swamp eel here?
All right, see you. Bye.
Hm.
Pond loach. Check.
-I've got it.
-Hey, wait.
There's no need to pay.
On the house.
-Hey, I feel bad about that.
-It's fine!
Every meal's free.
You should feel terrible.
Hey!
Hey, hey. I really wanna pay.
There's really no need.
-You're incredible! Bye.
-See ya next time. Bye.
Primordium. It's good
to see you after so long.
PRIMORDIUM
Fixer Primordium
does not report to anyone,
not even Fixer Celestial.
When Fixer Primordium reappears…
YEH YUEH TONG WATCH LIST, S-TIER FIXER
MALE, AGE 36 TO 38
…it signifies a momentous
historical event will unfold.
STATUS: DECEASED
STATUS: NORMAL
FIXER WITH YEH YUEH TONG,
SPECIAL OPERATIONS UNIT
RELATED PERSONS: UNKNOWN